Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford Collection 0013.123.001
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
1978-2012
0013.123.001
18.0 Cubic feet 33 Boxes, scrapbooks, oversized materials
Scope and Contents note
Box 1: Administration, A-Correspondence, 1980s
Administration/Accessions and Loans, notebook, 1970s
Administration/Acquisitions, 1970s
Administration/Correspondence/1975
Administration/Correspondence/1976
Administration/Correspondence/1977
Administration/Correspondence/1978
Administration/Correspondence/1979
Administration/Correspondence/1980
Administration/Correspondence/1981
Administration/Correspondence/1982
Administration/Correspondence/1983
Administration/Correspondence/1984
Administration/Correspondence/1985
Administration/Correspondence/1986
Administration/Correspondence/1987
Administration/Correspondence/1988
Administration/Correspondence/1989
Box 2: Administration/Correspondence, 1990s-2000s
Administration/Correspondence/1990
Administration/Correspondence/1991
Administration/Correspondence/1992
Administration/Correspondence/1993
Administration/Correspondence/1994
Administration/Correspondence/1995
Administration/Correspondence/1996
Administration/Correspondence/1997
Administration/Correspondence/1998
Administration/Correspondence/1999
Administration/Correspondence/2000
Administration/Correspondence/2001
Administration/Correspondence/2002
Administration/Correspondence/Archives/Margaret Mair/2000s
Administration/Correspondence/Genealogy Inquiries and Responses, 1970s-2000s
Box 3: Administration/Equipment – Board of Directors/Meeting Notices
Administration/Eqipment//Ikon-105 Capital copier, 2000s
Administration/Equipment/A-copy Cannon Copier, 1990s
Administration/Librarian's reports, 1976-1983
Administration/Museum Assessment/MAP, Marsha Lotstein has as of 6/29/05
Administration/Museum Assessment/MAP I/administrative material, 1997
Administration/Mission Statement, c. 1990s
Administration/Museum Assessment, 1997
Administration/Staff
Administration/Staff/Executive Directors/Lotstein, 1982-2004
Administration/Staff/Executive Directors/Kafer, Estelle, 2004-
Administration/Staff/Rudolph, Shayna/Aliyah, 2007
Administration/Staff/Job descriptions
Awards and proclamations
Board of Directors/By-laws
Board of Directors/Executive Committee
Board of Directors/Incorporation Papers
?Board of Directors/Letters to File removed?
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1971-1980/Emma Cohen
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1980-1982/M.Delott Garber
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1982-1987/Morris Handler
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1987-1992/Joseph Hurwitz
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1992-1994/Jerry Wagner
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1994-1996/Leon Chameides
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1996-1998/Seymour Saltzman
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1998-2001/David Klau
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/2001-2002/Lea Rubenstein
Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/2004-/Art Nassau
Box 4: Board of Directors/Meetings - Board of Directors/Minutes/M. Delott Garber
Board of Directors/Meetings/President Emma Cohen's notes, 1971-1980
Board of Directors/Members/1971-1981
Board of Directors/Members/1979-1980
Board of Directors/Members/1982-1992
Board of Directors/Members/1993-2003
Board of Directors/Members/1996-1997
Board of Directors/Members/2005-2006
Board of Directors/Members/Presidents/
Board of Directors/Members/Presidents/Cohen, Emma/Correspondence, 1970s
Board of Directors/Members/Presidents/Cohen, Emma/Notebook, 1970s
Board of Directors/Minute Book, earliest minutes, 1970s
Board of Directors/Minutes/1970s
Board of Directors/Minutes/1982/M. Delott Garber
Box 5: Board of Directors/Minutes/Morris Handler – Z
Board of Directors/Minutes/1982-1987/Morris Handler
Board of Directors/Minutes/1987-1992/Joseph Hurwitz
Board of Directors/Minutes/1992-1994/Jerry Wagner
Board of Directors/Minutes/1994-1996/Leon Chameides
Board of Directors/Minutes/1996-1998/Seymour Saltzman
Board of Directors/Minutes/1998-2000/David Klau
Board of Directors/Minutes/2001-2002/Lea Rubenstein
Board of Directors/Minutes/2003-/Arthur Nassau
Board of Directors/Miscellaneous/1990s-2000s
Board of Directors/Nominating Committee/Notes by President Emma Cohen 1970s
Board of Directors/Program Committee, 1970s
Board of Directors/Program Committee, 1980s
Board of Directors/Program Committee, 1990s
Box 6: Conferences
Conferences/1991/American Jewish Historical Society Conference in Hartford/One box of materials
Box 7: Exhibits, 1960s-1970s
Exhibit files are filed chronologically by date of installation. Exhibit panels of many of the larger exhibits are currently (August 2006) filed in large flat boxes on the exhibit shelves. See also scrapbooks and oversize.
Exhibits/1968/Lower East Side and Hartford Jews
Exhibits/1975/Emanuel Synagogue/American Jewish Experience
Exhibits/1975/Long Time Residents of the Hartford Area
Exhibits/1976/Exhibits/Bicentennial
Exhibits/1976/Ruth Wyllys Chapter, DAR/Photographs of Early Hartford Scenes
Exhibits/1976/Scott-Fanton Museum, Danbury/Jewish Life in Connecticut since 1976
Exhibits/1977/Emanuel Synagogue/Discovery: Our Fathers and Grandfathers
Exhibits/1977/Lewis Fox
Exhibits/1977/Our Community At Work
Exhibits/1977/South Windsor Library/Old Hartford and Jewish War Veterans
Exhibits/1978/Sixty Years of Zionism
Exhibits/1978/Sixty Years of Zionism/Book, to be published, 2 folders
Box 8: Exhibits 1980s-2000s – Facilities (Decade of Destiny is boxed separately)
Exhibits/1980/Contribution of Hartford Jewry to the City's Arts
Exhibits/1981/Avon Public Library/Jewish History in the Hartford Area
Exhibits/1981/Windsor Public Library/Fox Family
Exhibits/1981/Wood Memorial Library/Jewish Ceremonial Objects
Exhibits/1982/Emanuel Synagogue/Rabbi Israel Goldfarb
Exhibits/1983/Jewish Family Expo
Exhibits/1985/A Shayna Maidel
Exhibits/1985/Hartford's Jewish Community: Yesterday and Today
Exhibits/1986/West Hartford Public Library/Yiddish documents, Newspapers, and Ephemera
Exhibits/1987/Agudas Achim/100th Anniversary. See also one oversize box of exhibit materials in Aisle 9
Exhibits/1988/Annie Fisher: A Remembrance 1883-1968
Exhibits/1995/Holocaust room
Exhibits/1996/The Way We Were
Exhibits/1998/Israel at 50
Exhibits/1999/Portraits of New Americans
Exhibits/1999/The Passover Haggadah: a Jewish Cultural Phenomenon
Exhibits/2004/Charter Oak Temple/ photographs
Exhibits/2000s/Synagogues, 3 oversize boxes and one pile of panels not in boxes
Exhibits/2007/Hartford Remembers Sophie Tucker, see also Families and Individuals/Tucker, Sophie
Exhibits/2008/"Documenting Life and Destruction: Emanuel Ringelbum and the Oneg Shabbes Archive"
Exhibits/2008/"The Hartford-Israel Connection: A Century of Commitment"
Exhibits/2008/Israel at 60
Exhibits/2010/A Reason to Remember
Facilities/Community Services Building, 2000s
Facilities/Jewish Community Center
Facilities/Jewish Community Center/Open House, 1991
Box 8a: Facilities/Buildings
Box 8b: Facilities/Buildings/Community Services Building, 2006
Boxes 9-14: Exhibits/1992/Decade of Destiny and Anne Frank in the World. These exhibits were planned jointly with the Connecticut Historical Society. Note: there is currently (12/21/05 no Box 12)
Box 15: Financial/Check Stubs
Financial/Check Stubs/1011-1160, 2/15/96-5/15/97
Financial/Check Stubs/1461-1535, 7/21/99-12/27/99
Financial/Check Stubs/1536-1601, 12/30/99-5/26/00
Financial/Check Stubs/1611-1685
Financial/Check Stubs/1651-1800, 6/3/86-4/25/88
Financial/Check Stubs/1686-1760, 10/10/00-2/28/01
Financial/Check Stubs/1761-1835, 2/25/01-7/16/01
Financial/Check Stubs/1801-1950, 5/1/88-10/1/89
Financial/Check Stubs/1911-1985, 7/12/01-11/28/01
Financial/Check Stubs/1951-2100, 10/15/89-2/21/91
Financial/Check Stubs/2101-2250, 2/28/91-5/30/92
Financial/Check Stubs/2251-2400, 6/11/92-10/15/93
Financial/Check Stubs/2401-2550, 10/18/93-12/30/94
Financial/Check Stubs/2551-2680, 12/30/94-1/18/96
Box 16 and 17: Financial/Deposit Slips, budget, matching grants, taxes Box 17, last few folders: Fundraising.
Financial/Deposit Slips, FY 1996
Financial/Deposit Slips, FY 1997
Financial/Deposit Slips, FY 1998
Financial/Deposit/Membership, 1988-1996
Financial/First Bank of West Hartford/CD, 1994-1995
Financial/First Bank of West Hartford/CD, 1996
Financial/Funding/Jewish Federation
Financial/Matching Allocations, 1990-1991; 1991-1992
Financial/Matching Allocations, 1992-1993
Financial/Matching Allocations, 1993-1994
Financial/Matching Allocations, 1994-1996
Financial/Matching Allocations, 1996-1997
Financial/Matching Allocations, 1997-1998
Financial/Matching Allocations, 1998-1999
Financial/Budget, 1980s
Financial/Budget, 1990-1992
Financial/Budget, 1992-1993
Financial/Budget, 1994
Financial/Budget, 1995
Financial/Budget, 1996-1996
Financial/Budget, 1998
Financial/Budget, 1999
Financial/Budget, 1990-
Financial/Deposit Record, 1996
Financial/Deposit Record, 1997
Financial/Tax Records, 1991-1993
Financial/Tax Records, 1994-1996
Financial/Tax Returns, 1991-1993
Financial/Tax Returns, 1994-1996
Financial/Tax Returns, 1995-
Fundraising/Endowment Funds, 1990s-2000s
Fundraising/Grants/Endowment, 1985
Fundraising/Used Book Sale, 1992
Grants/Endowment Foundation Transition Funds Request, Jewish Community Foundation, 2004
Box 18: Hall of Fame, 1980s
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1982
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1983/Newspaper clippings
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1984
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1985
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1986
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1987
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1988
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1989
Box 19: 1990s-2000s
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1990
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1992
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1995
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1995
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1997
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1997
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1998
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/2002
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/Honorees
Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/Policies and Procedures
Box 20: Historical Highlights - Meetings and Programs (other than annual meetings), 1970s-1980s
Meetings and Programs are filed chronologically by date of event.
Historical Highlights Meetings and Programs/1970s-1980s/Guest Book
Meetings and Programs/1971 Sept. 9/Bernard Wax
Meetings and Programs/1972 June 28/ Judge Abraham S. Borden
Meetings and Programs/1972 May 10/Berthold Gaster
Meetings and Programs/1973 June 13/Cantor Arthur Koret
Meetings and Programs/1974 Dec. 12/Mt. Sinai Hospital/Dr. Isadore Geeter
Meetings and Programs/1974 June 19/Rabbi Avrutnick interview
Meetings and Programs/1974 Nov 22/Rae Neiditz interview
Meetings and Programs/1974 Nov. 6/Mark Sobotka interview
Meetings and Programs/1974 Sept. 22/Hartford Jews 1900-1925, documentary
Meetings and Programs/1975 April 22/Jenny Silver interview
Meetings and Programs/1975 Jan. 10/Herman Holz interview
Meetings and Programs/1975 March 3/Judge George Schwolsky interview
Meetings and Programs/1975 March 31/Rabbi Arthur A. Chiel "stiles and the Jews"
Meetings and Programs/1975 May 12/Melvin W. Title interview
Meetings and Programs/1975 Nov. 3/Bill Savitt interview
Meetings and Programs/1975 Oct. 8/Ezra Melrose interview
Meetings and Programs/1976 Feb. 11/Judge Leo Parsky
Meetings and Programs/1976 March 28/Rabbi Reuven Kimelman/Bibles' impact on founding fathers
Meetings and Programs/1976 May 12/Sadie Klau interview
Meetings and Programs/1976 Nov. 10/Judge Joseph Blumenfeld interview
Meetings and Programs/1976 Oct. 13/Emma Cohen Interview
Meetings and Programs/1976? /Mariana and David Eckstein/Russian Emigrants
Meetings and Programs/1977 April 13/Rabbi Philip Lazowski interview/
Meetings and Programs/1977 December 8/Berthold Gaster interview
Meetings and Programs/1977 February 9/Rita Cohn Interview
Meetings and Programs/1977 January 12/Judge Harry H. Kleinman interview
Meetings and Programs/1977 March 9/Moses Neiditz Interview
Meetings and Programs/1977 November 9/Seymour Saltzman/Making Your Family Tree
Meetings and Programs/1978 December 13/Henry D. Margolis/The Margolis Family of Craftsmen
Meetings and Programs/1978 June 2/History of the Reform Movement in Hartford/Rabbi Harold Silver
Meetings and Programs/1978 March 8/Rabbi Abraham Avrutnick/History of the Orthodox Movement in Hartford
Meetings and Programs/1978 May 18/History of the Conservative Movement in Hartford/Rabbi Stanley Kessler
Meetings and Programs/1978 September 13/Stephen Joel Trachtenberg
Meetings and Programs/1979 April 4/Holocaust Commemoration/Peter Korduner interview
Meetings and Programs/1979 December 12/Fran Waltman/Yiddish Theater in Hartford 1901-1910
Meetings and Programs/1979 March 14/Alfred Weisel/the History of Jewish Education in the Greater Hartford Area
Meetings and Programs/1979 May 9, Dr. M. Delott Garber, interview
Meetings and Programs/1979 November 8/Ethnic History of Hartford – videotape
Meetings and Programs/1979 October11/Golden Age of Jewish Music in Hartford/Cantor Arthur Koret
Meetings and Programs/1980 April 10/Holocaust Commemoration/Rabbi Hans Bodenheimer
Meetings and Programs/1980 February 20/Daniel Peer
Meetings and Programs/1980 March 13/Daniel Peer, Scholar-in-Residence/The Current Political Situation in the Mideast
Meetings and Programs/1980 May 8/Rabbi Howard Berman The Beauty of Holiness
Meetings and Programs/1980 November 13/Irving and Belle Berkowetz Cutler (COPACO)
Meetings and Programs/1980 October 9/Soviet Synagogues and Refusenicks visited
Meetings and Programs/1981 November 1/Prof. Walter Cahn at Trinity College
Meetings and Programs/1982 February 22/Contemporaary Israel: An American Settler's Perspective/Robert Rockaway/
Meetings and Programs/1982 March 4/Robert A. Rockaway/American Jewish Congress, joint program
Meetings and Programs/1982 May 19/Our Society: A Look at the Future
Meetings and Programs/1982 September 9/Jerry Wagner Interview
Meetings and Programs/1983 April 14/How the Fiddler got on the Roof
Meetings and Programs/1983 December 8/Bert Welk Interview
Meetings and Programs/1983 March 10/The Greater Hartford Jewish Federation: Its History, Growth, and Development
Meetings and Programs/1984 December 13/Meet the Author: Kenneth Libo
Meetings and Programs/1984 June 14/An Evening with David T. Chase
Meetings and Programs/1984 May 10/Dr. Leonard Menczer
Meetings and Programs/1984 November 8/An evening at the Connecticut Historical Society
Meetings and Programs/1984 September 13/The First Experience: the Immigrant and the Statue of Liberty/Ira Yellin
Meetings and Programs/1984/Precious Legacy
Meetings and Programs/1985 April 25/An Interview with Simon Konover
Meetings and Programs/1985 June 27/Arlene Neiditz and Vivian Zoë
Meetings and Programs/1985 March 14/Dr. Nathan Mayer/A Research Study by Dr. Irving
Meetings and Programs/1986 March 16/An Exclusive Interview with Julius Berman
Meetings and Programs/1986 September 30/Dr. Jonathan Rosenbaum
Meetings and Programs/1987 April 23/Herman Holtz re Ados Israel
Meetings and Programs/1987 March 12/Ellsworth Grant
Meetings and Programs/1988 April 5/Hartford in 1948
Meetings and Programs/1989 April 4/David Dalin/Researching and Writing Local Jewish History
Meetings and Programs/1989 April 6/A Celebration of Yiddish Musical Theatre
Meetings and Programs/1989 Dec. 6/JCC book and Craft Fair/Lothar Kahn, Irving Waltman, David Dalin
Meetings and Programs/1989 March 16\Records Management in Synagogues
Box 21: Meetings and Programs (Other than Annual Meetings 1990s-2000s
Meetings and Programs/ca. 1990s/14th Annual Jewish Book Festival
Meetings and Programs/1991 Nov. 4/Henry Levy Interview
Meetings and Programs/1991 November 20/Hartford's South End/Irving and Fran Waltman
Meetings and Programs/1993 November 14/Paid Up Membership/Joan Rosenbaum
Meetings and Programs/1993/Historical Research Through Personal Perspective
Meetings and Programs/1994 March 10/Stave and Sunderland, From the Old Country
Meetings and Programs/1994 Oct. 19/Irving Waltman interview
Meetings and Programs/1995 Nov. 5/Rabbi Hillel Silverman
Meetings and Programs/1996 March 12/Leon Chameides/Jews of Prague
Meetings and Programs/1996 May 14/Joyce Miller/They Came for Good
Meetings and Programs/1997 Dec. 7/Paid Up Membership/Ann Louise Gittleman
Meetings and Programs/1997-1998/Yiddish Festival
Meetings and Programs/1998 December. 20/Paid Up Membership/Arik Rosenblum
Meetings and Programs/1998 June 4/Scrapbooking
Meetings and Programs/1998 May 3/Rabbi Haskel Lendenthal interview
Meetings and Programs/1998 November 10/Lita Weis Marks, Time's Tapestry
Meetings and Programs/1998/Connecticut Visions, with Connecticut Historical Society
Meetings and Programs/1999 April 11/Yiddle on his Fiddle
Meetings and Programs/1999 April 19/Remembering Abraham Goldstein
Meetings and Programs/1999 April 23/Passover Haggadah
Meetings and Programs/1999 Nov. 21/200 Years of an American Ethnic Family
Meetings and Programs/1999/Paid up Membership/Bernard Lurie
Meetings and Programs/1999-2000/Ideas
Meetings and Programs/1999-2000/Yiddish Festival
Meetings and Programs/2000 Nov. 5/Dr. Leon Chameides
Meetings and Programs/2001 April 22/Heritage Award
Meetings and Programs/2001 Nov. 18/Marjorie Rafal
Meetings and Programs/2001/May-June/Visas for Life
Meetings and Programs/2002/Anniversaries/30th/Honoring Past Presidents
Meetings and Programs/2003/Jews of Kaifeng
Meetings and Programs/2003/Yiddish Festival
Meetings and Programs/2004/Arnold Dashefsky, the American Jewish Experience: 1654-2004
Meetings and Programs/2004/Rabbi Okalika
Meetings and Programs/2006/Voices of Philanthropy
Meetings and Programs/2007/Annual Meeting
Meetings and Programs/2007/Joyce Antler
Meetings and Programs/2007/Margolis Furniture
Meetings and Programs/2008
Meetings and Programs/2008/Jews of China
Meetings and Programs/2008/Scream the Truth at the World: Emanuel Ringelblum and the Hidden Archive of the Warsaw Ghetto
Meetings and Programs/2009
Meetings and Programs/April 26, 2009/ Leon Chameides presentation on Mount Sinai (includes PowerPoint on CD) see Mount Sinai collection, box 4
Meetings and Programs/2009/Jews of the Venetian Ghetto
Meetings and Programs/2010/Echoes and Reflections
Box 21a: Programs and Events
The program and events collection includes publicity, press and information about various programs sponsored or containing information gleaned from the Historical Society. The collection is arranged chronologically.
"Out of the Archives" –
Sophie Tucker Exhibit, June 3, 2007
North End Project, February 8, 2008 –
National Yiddish Book Center, April 6, 2008
"Scream the Truth at the World: Emanuel Ringlebloom…" April 11, 2008
Doris and Simon Konover Event, September 7, 2008
Senator Dodd, September 14, 2008
Virginia Hale's Beatrice Fox Aurbach Book Talk, October 30, 2008
"Oral History – How to do it? Why to do it?" September 29, 2008
"The Jews of China"
Time Capsule, January 16, 2009
Lecture by Brandeis Professor Joyce Antler, October 18, 2009
Box 21a: Programs & Events
Historical Society Programs and Events/Celebrating 30 Years
Historical Society Programs and Events/JHS Schwartz
Historical Society Programs and Events/"Out of the Archives"
Historical Society Programs and Events/Sophie Tucker Exhibit
Historical Society Programs and Events/North End Project
Historical Society Programs and Events/National Yiddish Book Center
Historical Society Programs and Events/"Scream the Truth at the World: Emanuel Ringlebloom…."
Historical Society Programs and Events/"Doris and Simon Konover Event"
Historical Society Programs and Events/Senator Dodd
Historical Society Programs and Events/Workshop/Oral History-How to do it? Why to do it?
Historical Society Programs and Events/"Virginia Hale's Beatrice Fox Aurbach Book Talk
Historical Society Programs and Events/"The Jews of China"
Historical Society Programs and Events/Time Capsule
Historical Society Programs and Events/Lecture by Brandeis Professor Joyce Antler
Historical Society Programs and Events/Recalling 500 Blue Hills Ave
Historical Society Programs and Events/Roth Exhibit
Historical Society Programs and Events/Historical Photos for Programs
Historical Society Programs and Events 2002-2008
Historical Society Programs and Events/Misc 2009
Historical Society Programs and Events/Misc 2010
Historical Society Programs and Events/Misc 2011
Historical Society Programs and Events/ 40th Anniverary Celebration/2011-2012
Box 22: Meetings and Programs/Annual Meetings – Members and Membership/Membership Lists
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1972/First Annual Meeting/Franchon Title interview
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1976/Bernard Wax
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1977/Samuel D. Kassow
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1979/Doris Schwartz Hurwit
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1980/Honoring Emma Cohen/Bernard Wax speaker
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1982/Benjamin Varon
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1985/Irving and Fran Waltman
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1987/Emma Cohen Jewish History Awards
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1988/Dr. Kenneth Libo People in Print
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1990/Gertude Ogushwitz
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1991/20th Anniversary/Henry S. Cohn
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1994/Bernard Wax/Tribute to Marsha Lotstein
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1995/Lenn Zonder
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1996/Jonathan Rosenbaum
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1997/25th Anniversary/Llyn Kaimowitz
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1998/John W. Shannahan
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/1999/Dr. David Shuldiner
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/2000/Dr. Betty Hoffman
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/2001/Vivian Zoë
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/2002/David Jacobs
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/2007/Elliot Pollock
Meetings and Programs/Annual Meeting/2007/Elliot Pollock
Meetings and Programs/OVERSIZE, in oversize box on shelf
Meetings and Programs/undated/Honorable Saul Seidman interview
Members and Membership/1980s/Annual Members
Members and Membership/Life Memberships
Members and Membership/Life Memberships/solicitation/1994-1995
Members and Membership/Membership Letters/1980s
Members and Membership/Membership Letters/1990s
Members and Membership/Membership Letters/n.d.
Members and Membership/Membership Lists/1988
Members and Membership/Membership Lists/1992
Members and Membership/Membership Lists/1993
Members and Membership/Membership Lists/1996
Members and Membership/Membership Lists/1997-1998
Members and Membership/Membership Lists/1999
Members and Membership/Membership Lists/2000
Members and Membership/Membership Lists/2001
Box 23: Members and Membership/New Members - Organizations
Members and Membership/New Members/1988-1989/1989-1990/1990-1991
Members and Membership/New Members/1992-1993
Members and Membership/New Members/1993-1994
Members and Membership/New Members/1994-1995 and 1995-1996
Members and Membership/New Members/1996-1997
Members and Membership/New Members/1997-1998
Members and Membership/New Members/1998-1999
Members and Membership/New Members/1999-2000
Members and Membership/Prospective Member List and Letter
Newsletters – see boxes 23a and 23b
Newspapers Clippings/1970s
Newspapers Clippings/1980s
Newspapers Clippings/1990s
Newspaper Clippings/2000s
Organizations/GHJCC/Book Festival/1993-1996
Organizations/GHJCC/Book Festival/1997-1999
Organizations/GHJCC/Book Festival/2000-2003
Organizations/Trinity College/Hillel
Box 23a: Newsletters, 1970s-1980s
Box 23b: Newsletters, 1990s-2003
Box 23c: Newsletters, 2004-
Newsletters 2004-2006